<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ActividadPerros</string>
    <string name="titulo">Top 5 Smartest Dogs!</string>
    <string name="border">Border Collie</string>
    <string name="descriocionberder">Considered the most intelligent dog of all, the Border Collie is capable of remembering more than 200 different commands and, in addition, enjoys learning both physical and mental skills. His great aptitude for work makes his education easy and rewarding. These dogs require consistent training and good socialization. The Border collie dog is in a constant state of alert, so it is very important to teach him when he should rest. It is a breed that has a great ability to perform tricks, which usually positions them at the top of skill contests.
However, as we have mentioned, these dogs learn very quickly, even negative behaviors. For this reason, we must try to have experience when teaching these dogs in order to avoid any errors in education.</string>
    <string name="caniche">Caniche or Poddle</string>
    <string name="descripcioncaniche">Not only is it one of the most elegant dogs. The poodle is characterized by its great ability to learn tricks, hence its enormous presence in competitions. These dogs love to run, pick up things with their mouths, and swim. They are very easy to train as long as it is with positive reinforcement and kind words. It is recommended to spend between 5 and 10 minutes a day for a good education of the poodle, improving communication and obedience. The memory of these dogs is exceptional, as they can remember a multitude of words and commands in just a few minutes. Their incredible adaptation and behavior with humans makes them great therapy dogs.</string>
    <string name="pastor">Pastor Aleman</string>
    <string name="descripcionpastor">The German Shepherd, as its name indicates, its work throughout history has been as a herding dog, thanks to its great skills of protection and surveillance of places and animals. Currently, the German Shepherd holds positions in the police as service, protection and rescue dogs. It is a very sensitive and delicate breed, so it requires a lot of attention and affection for its education and correct learning. His great mental, physical and cognitive abilities are what position him among the most intelligent races. Although they have a great facility for learning and a great desire to learn and work, if they are not educated correctly, their behavior can cause problems.</string>
    <string name="golden">Golder Retriever</string>
    <string name="descripciongolden">This beautiful dog is capable of taking on a wide variety of tasks. They are ideal for working as police drug search dogs and as rescue dogs. In addition, their great sociability and cordial character make them great dogs for the company of children and, in many cases, for people with special care. Also, they are great for both physical and psychological therapy. The Golden Retriever is focused on a task until it is finished and adapts very well to day-to-day situations, taking part in all the activities in which his caretaker is involved.</string>
    <string name="dobermann">Dobermann</string>
    <string name="descripciondobermann">Placed in the top 5 of the ranking, this breed learns the commands it is taught very quickly. It is a very sociable and active dog that hates loneliness. The Doberman usually works as a guard dog and protection of people and farms, since they are very loyal to their caregivers. Daily training is very important, as they are very energetic dogs, which makes them stand out in agility tests. To do this, exercises such as jumping jacks and discus throws can be performed. They can become aggressive if they dont discharge enough energy. An early and positive training of the Doberman is essential so that his abilities are properly developed.</string>
</resources>